<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <template id="mis_popi_act.consent" name="POPI Act Consent Form">
        <t t-name="mis_popi_act.POPIActConsent">
            <t t-call="website.layout">
                <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure oe_empty">
                    <div class="popiact">
                        <div id="popiactModal" class="modal fade" tabindex="-1" data-backdrop="static" data-keyboard="false">
                            <div class="modal-dialog modal-lg">
                                <div class="modal-content">
                                    <div class="modal-header">
                                        <h4 class="modal-title">Protection of Personal Information Act</h4>
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="modal-body">
                                        <h5><u>Consent to Process information in terms of the Protection of Personal Information Act, 2013 (POPI)</u></h5>
                                        <p class="text-secondary">
                                            The Insurance Sector Education and Training Authority (INSETA) welcomes you to it’s INSETA Management Information System (MIS).  By using the 
                                            MIS you hereby acknowledge that you have read the following Protection of Personal Information notice.
                                        </p>
                                        <h5><u>Collection of Personal Information</u></h5>
                                        <p class="text-secondary">
                                            The INSETA will only collect personal information consistent with the purpose for which it is required.  Personal information relating to an 
                                            identifiable living, natural person, and where it is applicable, an identifiable, existing juristic person, as defined in the Protection of 
                                            Personal Information Act, 2013 that the INSETA may collect, includes but is not limited to:
                                            <ul style="margin-left:32px">
                                                <li>information relating to the race, gender, sex, national, ethnic or social origin, color, age, physical or mental health, well-being, disability, religion, culture, language and birth of the person;</li>
                                                <li>information relating to the education or the medical, financial, criminal or employment history of the person;</li>
                                                <li>any identifying number, symbol, email address, physical address, telephone number, location information, online identifier or other particular assignment to the person;</li>
                                                <li>the biometric information of the person;</li>
                                                <li>the personal opinions, views or preferences of the person;</li>
                                                <li>correspondence sent by the person that is implicitly or explicitly of a private or confidential nature or further correspondence that will reveal the contents of the original correspondence;</li>
                                                <li>the views or opinions of another individual about the person; and</li>
                                                <li>the name of the person if it appears with other personal information relating to the person or of the disclosure of the name itself will reveal information about the person.</li>
                                            </ul>
                                            There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by the INSETA.  This information can include your:  
                                            IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses, if applicable.
                                        </p>
                                        <h5><u>Use of Personal Information</u></h5>
                                        <p class="text-secondary">
                                            The INSETA uses personal information primarily to:
                                            <ul style="margin-left:32px">
                                                <li>authenticate a user of the MIS;</li>
                                                <li>provide a user with access to the MIS;</li>
                                                <li>communicate requested information to the user;</li>
                                                <li>communicate with the INSETA stakeholders;</li>
                                                <li>provide services to the User as requested by the user;</li>
                                                <li>maintain the quality of services provided by the INSETA;</li>
                                                <li>conduct research about programmes/services offered by the INSETA, and </li>
                                                <li>provide general statistics regarding use of the MIS.</li>
                                            </ul>
                                        </p>

                                        <h5><u>Protection of Personal Information Act</u></h5>
                                        <p class="text-secondary">
                                            The INSETA will not sell, rent, or lease personal information to third parties.  
                                            The INSETA will disclose your personal, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:
                                            <ul style="margin-left:32px">
                                                <li>conform to the provisions of any law in force from time to time or comply with legal process served on the INSETA or the website;</li>
                                                <li>protect and defend the rights or property of the INSETA; and</li>
                                                <li>to protect the personal safety of users of the INSETA, or the public.</li>
                                            </ul>
                                        </p>

                                        <h5><u>Security of Personal Information</u></h5>
                                        <p class="text-secondary">
                                            The INSETA will take all reasonable measures in line with any law and/or the INSETA policies to ensure that personal information 
                                            is protected and secured during collection, storage, transfer, processing and use of personal information.
                                        </p>

                                        <h5><u>Contact Person Information</u></h5>
                                        <p class="text-secondary">
                                            Any questions relating to the INSETA’s treatment of personal information maybe addressed to the  to the Chief Executive Officer below:
                                            <br/>
                                            The INSETA Chief Executive Officer<br/>
                                            Email Address:  Gugum@inseta.org.za<br/>
                                            Telephone number:  011 381 8900
                                        </p>

                                        <h5><u>Declaration and informed Consent</u></h5>
                                        <p class="text-secondary">
                                            I declare that I am permitted to supply personal information to the INSETA for the purpose of access and 
                                            use of the MIS, and related legal and operational reasons.   This information is also accurate, up-to-date, 
                                            and  is not misleading. It  is complete in all respects.  I undertake to immediately advise the INSETA of any changes 
                                            to personal information should any of these details change.  I furthermore give the INSETA permission to process personal
                                            information as provided above, and acknowledge that 
                                            I understand the purposes for which it is required,  as well as for the  purpose  for which it will be used. 
                                            <br/><br/>
                                            Please place a tick in the POPI Act Consent check-box indicating your agreement to the above conditions. <br/>
                                            Finally, please click on the Submit button. 
                                            <br/><br/>
                                            <div class="form-check mb-1">
                                                <input type="checkbox" class="form-check-input" id="checkboxAgree"/>
                                                <label class="form-check-label" for="checkboxAgree"><b>POPI Act Consent</b></label>
                                            </div>

                                        </p>
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="modal-footer">
                                        <button id="buttonDoNotAgree" type="button" class="btn btn-link text-decoration-none">
                                            I do not agree
                                        </button>
                                        <button id="buttonAgree" type="button" class="btn btn-primary">Submit</button>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </t>
        </t>
    </template>

</odoo>